Fredrik Gustafson

Product Manager - Web Developer

With a demonstrated history of creating, maintaining and managing product and teams. My strengths lay in **creativity** with regards to problem-solving, innovation and **learning**. But mostly it's my **transparent** approach and depth in working with teams, that gives me the edge.

By nature I always seek to **create solutions**, now after three years experience in **leading** product development for a SaaS start-up, I am advancing in **Full-Stack Web Development**. I thrive in an environment where I can utilize my strengths by taking **ideas to reality** collaborating with other creative minds

Experience

2016-01 - CPO

present VQuarter AB - Stockholm/Spain

B2B SaaS product for vacation rental managers & property managers.

- Products managed: web applications, 2x IOS app, 2x Android App.
- · Managed cross-functional teams.
- Defined product vision, strategy and roadmap from idea to release.
- Lead 6 member engineering team.

2015-01 - Project Manager

2016-01 *VQuarter AB - Stockholm/Spain*

- Wire framed and designed web and mobile applications.
- Planed sprints, held scrum meetings.

2014-07 - Freelance

2015-04 Web Designer

- Created custom web pages from themes.
- Applied SEO knowledge to web pages & Implement Google Analytics.

2013-03 - Deckhand | Professional Race Crew

2014-05 S/Y Varsovie - *Ocean*

I am an active sailor with a strong love for the oceans and have been competing on an international level, **leading multinational sailing teams.** I've worked on super yachts and sailed across the Atlantic five times.

2012-05 - Sales

2012-12 Hi3g Access AB - *Stockholm*

Hired to "cold call" and promote Hi3g Access AB Internet and Mobile services.

- Placed sales calls to current or inquiring new customers.
- · Consistently achieved monthly sales goals.

Education

2018 University Of California, Los Angeles Extension - CA

Full-time intensive bootcamp 360 hours class hours 20+ hours personal coding per

week, build 18 responsive sites and web apps.

2009 - Östra Reals Gymnasium - *Stockholm*

2012 High School business diploma

2009 - Corona Del Mar High School - *CA*

2010 High School Exchange Student.

Certificates

2018 Full stack Web Development - UCLA

The personal expression | Communication Certification - *Stockholm*

2015 Digital Communication - Berghs School Of Communication Stockholm

Personal Info

Phone

US +1 714 203-4639

Phone

SWE +46 709456556

E-mail

fredrik.gustafson1@gmail.com

Date of birth

1992-09-25

WWW

imfredrik.com

GitHub

https://github.com/freddegurre

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/fredrik-

gustafson-a634b5114/

Skills

Leadership

•••••

Project Management

Software Development

Requirements Analysis

Agile / Scrum

Software

Javascript & JQuery,

HTML/CSS

Node.js with Express

React.js

MongoDB / MySQL